Muhammad Nazmi Bin Ismail

Address:

No. 12A, Jalan TPS 4/4, Taman Pelangi Semenyih, 43500 Semenyih, Selangor Darul Ehsan.

Selangor Darul Ehsan. Mobile: 017-3637187

Email: imuhammadnazmi@gmail.com



Objective

Motivated worker with six months of internship experience and nearly one year of experience as a Junior Software Developer. Seeking opportunities to apply and expand my skills in IT industry. Dedicated to continuously improving my programming skills, with a particular focus on deepening my knowledge of Python and web frameworks. I am committed to continuously learning about the industry and actively contributing to company success. Eager to take on more responsibilities and contribute to achieving organizational goals.

Education

Diploma in Electronic and Information Technology

July 2017 to Dec 2020 - German Malaysian Institute

CGPA: 3.52

Sijil Pelajaran Malaysia

Jan 2016 to Dec 2016 – Sekolah Menengah Kebangsaan Bandar Rinching

Result SPM: 1A 1A-1B+2B 2C+2D

Skill

I. Language Skills

Language	Spoken	Written
Malay Language	Excellent	Very good
English	Good	Good

II. Hard Skills

- Microsoft Word and Power Point
- Java Programming
- Android Mobile App Development
- Customer Service
- SQL Database
- Python Programming
- C# Programming
- Web Development

III. Soft Skills

- Leadership
- Critical Thinking
- Attention to Detail

Work Experience

Organization: Gross Synergy Sdn Bhd (July 2019 - December 2019)

Position: Intern (System Support)

- To get more experience in industry.
- To improve employer -value skill such as teamwork and communication.
- Learn to understand about Point of Sale (POS) system.
- Learn to handle databases.

Organization: Petronas Taman Pelangi Semenyih (March 2021 – June 2022)

Position: Cashier

- Managing transactions with customers using cash registers.
- Scanning goods and ensuring pricing is accurate.
- Collecting payments whether in cash or credit.
- Improving employer-value skill such as teamwork and communication.
- Maintain clean and tidy checkout areas.

Organization: Antaragrafik Systems Sdn Bhd (July 2022 – Present)

Position: Junior Software Developer

- Implementing the software on the web server.
- Diagnosing issues and performing software maintenance or configuration.
- Preparing supporting documentation.
- Learn to handle databases.
- Coordinating with other teams on integrating with other applications.

Achievement

Oct 2018 – MJII Robofighto Competition 2018

Participated in competing with the robot have been organized by Mara-Japan Industrial Institute (MJII).

Sep 2018 – Malaysia International Robotic Exhibition 2018

Participated in programming the Altino robot car for a collaboration that have been organized by Universiti Teknikal Malaysia Melaka with Scientific & Technical Products Sdn. Bhd.

Hobbies

- 1. Mobile gaming
- 2. Reading book
- 3. Study programming

References

1.

Name: MS ANNA POPOVA Name: MS AHADA BINTI KARIM

Position: Project Manager Position: Supervisor

Company: Company:

Antaragrafik Systems Sdn Bhd, Satria Sinar Enterprise,

1st Floor, North Wing Block, Petronas Taman Pelangi Semenyih,

Syed Kechik Foundation Building, Lot Pt 26796, Jalan TPS 1/5, Jalan Kapas, Bangsar Utama, Taman Pelangi Semenyih,

59100 Kuala Lumpur, 43500 Semenyih,

Kuala Lumpur Selangor Darul Ehsan

Mobile: 012-904 0475 Mobile: 012-384 1412